

# Felix J

Trichy 9042575202

felixanderson500@gmail.com

React Developer Having 3 years and 10 months of experience as Software Developer.

An adaptable and quick learner who has extensive knowledge in React and always looking to work in a challenging environment to utilize my technical and management skills for the growth of the organization as well as to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the IT sector

## **Work Experience**



## React Developer (DIH)

02/2023 to Present

#### Accenture

- · Implemented reusable components based on Ant design UI
- Configured Axios interceptors for error handling
- Used Redux to store data globally and for easy retrieval of data to any component in the app
- Implemented improvements to boost site performance.
- Used Typescript to add type safety to the project

## React Developer (McDonalds)

01/2023 to 02/2023

#### Accenture

- · Customized Material UI Modals based on client requirement
- Used React Router to turn application into Single Page Application
- Used Microsoft Authentication Library for authentication

#### ABAP Developer(SAP)

05/2022 to 01/2023

#### Accenture

- Developed License management for Sales order
- Worked on Outbound IDocs using change pointer
- Developed a FM to update the SCAC code and tracking number in Sales order header text

## **React Developer(Ford Motors)**

01/2021 to 04/2022

#### Infosys

- Developed highly-responsive user interface via React components
- Used React Router to turn application into Single Page Application
- Used Formik to create forms and for handling errors
- Used prede ned components from Material UI
- Followed Agile and Scrum model for the development of the product

## **Chatbot Developer(Ford Motors)**

05/2019 to 01/2021

#### Infosys

- · Worked on Chatbot Implementation for EWM
- Optimized web pages for maximum speed and scalability
- Developed 25 use case in chatbot to solve frequently occurring EWM related incidents
- Used Bootstrap for responsive web design
- Used Axios to communicate with APIs easily in React apps

#### Skills



Front-End: React JS, Redux, TypeScript, Javascript, HTML, SCSS.

UI Framework: Material UI, Ant Design, Bootstrap, Tailwind.

## Education



#### Saranathan college of engineering

Bachelor's

BE - Electronics and Communication engineering

06/2015 to 04/2019

## Bishop Heber higher secondary school

High school or equivalent

State board of school examination(HR.SEC)

## Railway Mixed higher secondary school

High school or equivalent State board of school examination(SEC)

06/2011 to 03/2013